Seeing is believing.
mother! is a drama, horror film directed by Darren Aronofsky.
A couple's relationship is tested when uninvited guests arrive at
their home, disrupting their tranquil existence.
Mother, played by Jennifer Lawrence.
Him, played by Javier Bardem.
Man, played by Ed Harris.
Woman, played by Michelle Pfeiffer.
Younger Brother, played by Brian Gleeson.
Oldest Son, played by Domhnall Gleeson.
(stylized as mother!) is a 2017 American psychological horror film written and directed by Darren Aronofsky, and starring
Jennifer Lawrence, Javier Bardem, Ed Harris, Michelle Pfeiffer, Domhnall Gleeson, Brian Gleeson, and Kristen Wiig.
Its plot follows a young woman whose tranquil life with her husband at their country home is disrupted by the
arrival of a mysterious couple, leading to a series of increasingly chaotic and destructive events.
The film premiered on September 5, 2017, at the 74th Venice International Film
Festival, where it was selected to compete for the Golden Lion.
It was released in the United States by Paramount
Pictures on September 15, 2017.
The film grossed $44.5 million worldwide.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
nightmare, nihilism, chaos, pregnancy.
The tone is dark and mind_bending and emotional.